[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110429pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 44, "question": "What a wonderful day to be British, don't you think, Anderson?", "question_tokens": ["What", "a", "wonderful", "day", "to", "be", "British", ",", "do", "n't", "you", "think", ",", "Anderson", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 45, "answer": "It's a good day to be a commoner, too, I think.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "a", "good", "day", "to", "be", "a", "commoner", ",", "too", ",", "I", "think", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Anderson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["RAF"]}, "docId": "110429pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NNS", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "WRB", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 51, "question": "Do you think that's going to be the moment or at least one of the key moments?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "that", "'s", "going", "to", "be", "the", "moment", "or", "at", "least", "one", "of", "the", "key", "moments", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "IN", "JJS", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 52, "answer": "Two moments, the moment she gets out of the car and reveals the dress, and in that moment, after the fly-by, when the RAF shoots past, and the big kiss happens.", "answer_tokens": ["Two", "moments", ",", "the", "moment", "she", "gets", "out", "of", "the", "car", "and", "reveals", "the", "dress", ",", "and", "in", "that", "moment", ",", "after", "the", "fly-by", ",", "when", "the", "RAF", "shoots", "past", ",", "and", "the", "big", "kiss", "happens", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110429pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 75, "question": "Do people still use that term here?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "people", "still", "use", "that", "term", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNS", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 76, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110429pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 77, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 78, "answer": "I don't like it very much.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "like", "it", "very", "much", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110429pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 117, "question": "What do brides worry about?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "brides", "worry", "about", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 118, "answer": "Don't fall over.", "answer_tokens": ["Do", "n't", "fall", "over", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110429pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 224, "question": "Cat, are you surprised that only -- there's only going to be one ring, that William is not going to wear a ring?", "question_tokens": ["Cat", ",", "are", "you", "surprised", "that", "only", "--", "there", "'s", "only", "going", "to", "be", "one", "ring", ",", "that", "William", "is", "not", "going", "to", "wear", "a", "ring", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "RB", ":", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "CD", "VBG", ",", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 225, "answer": "Yes, I was actually.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "was", "actually", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["William"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110429pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 230, "question": "You do?", "question_tokens": ["You", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 231, "answer": "I do.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110429pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 257, "question": "You were saying, you can't beat a man in a uniform, can you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "were", "saying", ",", "you", "ca", "n't", "beat", "a", "man", "in", "a", "uniform", ",", "can", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 258, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110429pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 427, "question": "Is there a tiara?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "a", "tiara", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 428, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110429pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 538, "question": "Wilt thou love her, comfort her, honor and keep her in sickness and in health, and forsaking all others, keep thee only unto her so long as ye both shall live?", "question_tokens": ["Wilt", "thou", "love", "her", ",", "comfort", "her", ",", "honor", "and", "keep", "her", "in", "sickness", "and", "in", "health", ",", "and", "forsaking", "all", "others", ",", "keep", "thee", "only", "unto", "her", "so", "long", "as", "ye", "both", "shall", "live", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "NN", "PRP$", ",", "NN", "PRP$", ",", "NN", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "CC", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", ",", "VB", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 539, "answer": "I will.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "will", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110429pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 540, "question": "Catherine Elizabeth, wilt thou have this man to thy wedded husband, to live together according to God's law in the holy estate of matrimony, wilt thou love him comfort him, honor and keep him, in sickness and in health, and forsaking all other, keep thee only unto him so long as ye both shall live?", "question_tokens": ["Catherine", "Elizabeth", ",", "wilt", "thou", "have", "this", "man", "to", "thy", "wedded", "husband", ",", "to", "live", "together", "according", "to", "God", "'s", "law", "in", "the", "holy", "estate", "of", "matrimony", ",", "wilt", "thou", "love", "him", "comfort", "him", ",", "honor", "and", "keep", "him", ",", "in", "sickness", "and", "in", "health", ",", "and", "forsaking", "all", "other", ",", "keep", "thee", "only", "unto", "him", "so", "long", "as", "ye", "both", "shall", "live", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "RP", "VBG", "TO", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "NN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "CC", "VB", "PRP", ",", "IN", "NN", "CC", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", ",", "VB", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 541, "answer": "I will.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "will", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Catherine Elizabeth"]}}]